Stuart Gerry Brown Papers
Stuart Gerry Brown Papers
- Correspondence
  - Rozwenc, Edwin Charles, See Amherst College.
  - Ruzicka, Thomas, 1952 (Box 8)
  - The Ryerson Press, 1951-1952 (Box 8)
  - R, miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - St. John, James Hamilton, See Payne Memorial Volume.
  - Salinger, Herman, See Grinnell College.
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Samuels, Charles, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Santayana, George, 1934 (Box 8)
  - The Saturday Review, 1952; 1964 (Box 8)
  - Sawyer, Michael O., See Syracuse University.
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., 1952-1962; 1967-1968,; undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Schmidt, Karl M., 1962; 1967 (Box 9)
  - Seward, William H., 1950 (Box 9)
  - Shaktman, Ben, See Syracuse University.
  - Shea, John J. B., 1956; 1959,; 1965-1967 (Box 9)
  - Shishkin, Hildegard, See Harriman, Averell.
  - Siffin, William, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
  - Simmons, Hans, See Payne Memorial Volume.
  - Simpson, Claude M., Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Simpson, George L. Jr., 1951 (Box 9)
  - Sinclair, Gregg Manners, 1950; 1962,; 1965 (Box 9)
  - Singer, Phillip, 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Smith, Grover, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Smith, M. Ellwood, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Smith, Thomas Vernor, 1949-1957; 1962-1964,; undated; includes letters from his daughters Gayle and Charlotte (Box 9)
  - Social Education (Journal), 1948; includes Lewis Paul Todd (Box 9)
  - The Society of American Historians, Inc., 1951-1954; undated (Box 9)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Spoehr, Alezander, See Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange between East & West.
  - Stalker, John N. "Jake", See University of Hawaii.
  - State of New York Division of the Budget, 1956-1957; undated; includes Paul Appleby (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) Albany, 1955 (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) at Buffalo, 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) Cortland, 1957; 1962 (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) College of Environmental Science and Forestry (ESF), 1955 (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) Harpur College, 1954-1955; 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - State University of New York (SUNY) Potsdam, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Stevens, Samuel, See Grinnell College; Payne Memorial Volume.
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1952-1967; undated; includes Roxanne Eberlein and Carol Evans; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. III, 1965 (Box 9)
  - The Stevenson Democratic Club, undated (Box 9)
  - Stevenson, John Fell, 1961; 1965 (Box 9)
  - Stewart, Milton D., 1956 (Box 9)
  - Story, Bascom, See Peace Corps.
  - Strebel, Ralph F., See Utica College.
  - Strong, Earl D., See Grinnell College; Payne Memorial Volume.
  - Sufrin, Sidney Charles, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Swerdlow, Irving, See Syracuse University.
  - Syracuse University, 1947-1953; includes Paul H. Appleby, Stephen Kemp Bailey, Kenneth Gill Bartlett, Carl R. Bye, Fina Goff Crawford, George Babcock Cressey, Eric H. Faigle, Sawyer Falk, A. Lee Fritschler, Donn V. Hart, Ann Hayes, Ralph E. Kharas, Gerard Mangone, William A. Miller, David Owen, Frank Peter Piskor, Roy Arthur Price, Michael O. Sawyer, Ben Shaktman, Irving Swerdlow, William Pearson Tolley, Richard G. Underwood, Clifford L. Winters Jr., Wayne Stewart Yenawine; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Syracuse University, 1954-1957; 1960-1968,; undated; 8 folders (Box 10)
  - S, miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Tapp, June and Robert, 1957; 1962-1963,; 1967,; undated (Box 11)
  - Tate, Allen, See Henry Holt & Company, Inc.
  - Taylor, George Rogers, See Amherst College.
  - Taylor, Harold, 1962-1965 (Box 11)
  - Thomas, Charles Wright, 1947-1949; 1952,; 1955,; undated (Box 11)
  - Thornton, Harrison J., See Payne Memorial Volume.
  - Thorp, Willard, 1947-1950; 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - Time Incorporated, 1955 (Box 11)
  - The Today Show, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Todd, Lewis Paul, See Social Education (Journal).
  - Tolley, William Pearson, See Syracuse University.
  - Tree, Marietta, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Triple Cities College, 1948-1950; Now Binghampton College, was attached to Syracuse University (Box 11)
  - Trivedi, R. K., 1962 (Box 11)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - T, miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Underwood, Richard G., See Syracuse University.
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, & Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - United States Army Staff College, 1957 (Box 11)
  - United States Civil Service Commission, 1962 (Box 11)
  - United States Department of State, 1951; 1966 (Box 11)
  - University of Chicago, 1950-1957; includes Charner Marquis Perry (Box 11)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1956; 1961-1962,; 1968 (Box 11)
  - University of Chicago Round Table, 1953-1955 (Box 11)
  - University of Hawaii, 1953; 1961-1968; includes Arthur Grove Day and John N. Stalker (Box 11)
  - University of Kansas City, 1947-1950; includes Hyatt Howe Waggoner (Box 11)
  - Utica College, 1954-1956; 1962-1967; was attched to Syracuse University; includes Ralph F. Strebel (Box 11)
  - U, miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Valverde, Walter, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Van Devender, Charles, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Vann, Carl R., 1957 (Box 11)
  - Volunteers for Stevenson, undated (Box 11)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review, 1949-1950; 1967 (Box 11)
  - V, miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - WSYR, 1948 (Box 11)
  - W. W. Norton & Co., Inc., 1948; 1968 (Box 11)
  - Wachman, Marvin, 1951-1957; 1965,; undated (Box 11)
  - Waggoner, Hyatt Howe, See University of Kansas City.
  - Walsh, Warren Bartlett, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Walters, Morgan L., 1961; 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - The Washington Post, 1953-1954 (Box 11)
  - Washington Square Press, Inc., 1962; 1965-1966 (Box 12)
  - Watkins, David D., 1949; 1954 (Box 12)
  - Waymack, William Wesley, 1948 (Box 12)
  - Whicher, George F., See Amherst College.
  - William Volker Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 12)
  - Winters, Clifford L., Jr., See Syracuse University.
  - Wise, Gene, 1962-1967; undated (Box 12)
  - Wolf, Frederick Barton, 1947; 1954-1955 (Box 12)
  - Wood, Paul Spencer, 1947-1953; undated (Box 12)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program, 1953-1955 (Box 12)
  - Works Projects Administration, 1942 (Box 12)
  - Wright, George C., 1948; 1952,; undated (Box 12)
  - Wyld, Lionel, 1965-1967; undated (Box 12)
  - W, miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - W, miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Yenawine, Wayne Stewart, See Syracuse University.
  - Y, miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Z, miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - First name only (Box 12)
  - Unidentified (Box 12)
- Memorabilia
  - Aden and the Middle East, 1962 (Box 13)
  - Application forms, U.S. Senate guest card (Box 13)
  - Biographical material, 1948-1960 (Box 13)
  - Biographies of others (Box 13)
  - Brochures and catalogues, 1948-1959 (Box 13)
  - Committees, Board of Graduate Studies, 1947-1951 (Box 13)
  - Course descriptions and teaching schedules, 1947-1961 (Box 13)
  - Expense accounts, 1950-1961 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1953-1961 (Box 13)
  - National Farmer's Union, 1950 (Box 13)
  - News clippings, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Photographs, S.G. Brown, A.E. Stevenson and others, 1952-1963 (Box 13)
  - Programs, Dinner and Round Table, 1953-1958 (Box 13)
  - Questions from the audience, holograph (Box 13)
  - Adlai E. Stevenson
    - Addresses and statements, 1961; reproduction, typescript (Box 13)
    - Addresses and statements, 1962; reproduction, typescript (Box 14)
    - News clippings, 1959-1962 (Box 14)
- Student records
  - Amirthanayagam, Guy, 1962-1963; includes correspondence (1962 only); See also Correspondence: Amirthanayagam, Guy. (Box 14)
  - Bain, Harry, 1961; See also Correspondence: Bain, Harry. (Box 14)
  - Baker, Donald, 1958; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Baker, Donald. (Box 14)
  - Bartle, Harrison Frederick, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Bodkin, Robert, 1959; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Bodkin, Robert. (Box 14)
  - Clarke, Robert (Box 14)
  - Cohn, Morton, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
  - Cooke, Robert, 1961; See also Correspondence: Cooke, Robert. (Box 14)
  - Cord, Robert L., 1960-1961; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Cord, Robert. (Box 14)
  - Farnen, Russell F., Jr., 1958-1960; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Farnen, Russell F., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Gibson, Frank F., 1960 (Box 14)
  - Goodwin, Paul, 1959; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Goodwin, Paul. (Box 14)
  - Lorenz, Robert A., 1960 (Box 14)
  - Mushkat, Jerome, See also Correspondence: Mushkat, Jerome. (Box 14)
  - Pickett, Robert S., 1963; correspondence (Box 14)
  - Riley, William A., 1961; correspondence; See also Correspondence: Riley, William A. (Box 14)
  - Roberts, Kenneth E., Jr., 1961 (Box 14)
  - Wise, Ralph Eugene, See also Correspondence: Wise, Ralph Eugene. (Box 14)
- Writings
  - Addresses
    - American Civilization and the Overseas Americans, CIA Training Program, Sep 21, 1960; holograph (Box 14)
    - The Citizen as Individual in American Society, typescript copy (Box 14)
    - The Citizen in Modern Society, typescript copy (Box 14)
    - Commencement Address at Lanai High School, 1968; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript rev. (Box 14)
    - Current Aspects of American Culture, May 22, 1948; original typescript (Box 14)
    - "Dissent in a Time of Tension", 1967; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 14)
    - The Idea of a College, Apr 22, 1948; draft A, typescript copy; draft B, original typescript rev., (Box 14)
    - On the Limits of Democracy, University of Akron, 1959-1960; holograph (Box 14)
    - Original Development of Democratic Political Philosophy, Air War College, Sep 15 1958 (Box 14)
    - Saved From Loneliness, Saved For Fellowship, Chapel, Nov 19 1947; original typescript (Box 14)
    - Some Observations on Stimulating Students to Greater Academic Achievement, Sep 12, 1957; typescript reproduction (Box 14)
    - Upstate vs. Downstate in New York Politics, outline, original typescript (Box 14)
    - The World and the Citizen, typescript reproduction (Box 14)
    - The World and the Individual, draft A, typescript revised; draft B, original typescript (Box 14)
    - Untitled
      - Council on the Humanities, University of Hawaii, 1965; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript rev.; draft C, repro. (Box 14)
      - Council on the Humanities, University of Hawaii, Oct 21, 1965; typescript reproduction (Box 14)
      - League of Women Voters broadcast, Dec 5, 1947; Nov 19, 1948;; undated; original typescript; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Addresses for Robert F. Kennedy, 1968; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript reproduction (Box 14)
    - Addresses for William Averell Harriman, holo., 1955; original and carbon typescript, includes research material (Box 14)
  - Articles
    - "Civil Disobedience", draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript reproduction (Box 14)
    - "Civil Rights and National Leadership: Eisenhower and Stevenson in the 1950's," reprint from Ethics, Jan. 1960 (Box 14)
    - "Considerations for an International Conference on the Ethics of Mutual Involvement", 1961; typescript reproduction (Box 14)
    - "Democracy, The New Conservatism and the Liberal Tradition in America," reprint from Ethics, Oct 1955, also draft A, original typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 14)
    - "Did the Conservatives 'Regain' Control of 'their' Republican Party", 1964; original typescript and related correspondence (Box 14)
    - "Dr. Johnson, Poetry and Imagination," reprint from Neophilologus (Box 15)
    - "Dr. Johnson and the Religious Problem," offprint from English Studies by R.W. Zandvoort (Box 15)
    - "Eisenhower and Stevenson in the McCarthy Era: A Study in Leadership," reprint Ethics, Jul 1959 (Box 15)
    - "Emerson," University of Kansas City Review, Autumn 1948, also typescript revised (Box 15)
    - "Emerson 1803-1953," reprint from Ethics, Apr 1954 (Box 15)
    - "Emerson in 1950", typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Emerson's Platonism," reprint from New England Quarterly, Sep 1945, also typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Ford Foundation Guides for Group Leaders", 1953-1954; holograph, original and typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "From Provincialism to the Great Community: the Social Philosophy of Josiah Royce," Ethics, Oct 1948 (Box 15)
    - "From Sword to Schoolbook," The University of Kansas City Review, Summer 1944 (Box 15)
    - Articles and definitions for Grolier Society Encyclopedia, originals and typescript copy revised (Box 15)
    - "Is a Kennedy draft Possible?", 1968; typescript rev. (Box 15)
    - "James Monroe", draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript reproduction rev. (Box 15)
    - "James Monroe," American-Oxford Encyclopedia, typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "James Monroe," Notes Catalog of Monroe's Book, photo print (Box 15)
    - "John Jay Chapman and the Emersonian Gospel," New England Quarterly, Jun 1952, also draft A, typescript copy; draft B, typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Legal and Political Philosophy", 1957; typescript reproduction (Box 15)
    - "The Mind of Thomas Jefferson," Ethics, Jan 1963 (Box 15)
    - "A Note on Poetry and Prophecy," Sewanee Review, Jan 1941 (Box 15)
    - "A Note on C. Ritter's Reading of Timaeus", reprint from Classical Philology, Apr 1941 (Box 15)
    - "Observations and Hume's Theory of Taste," offprint from English Studies by R.W. Zandvoort (Box 15)
    - "Organization, Strategy and Tactics of American Communists", outline, holo.; draft A, original typescript rev.; draft B typescript (Box 15)
    - "Plural Values and the Neutral State: The American Doctrine of the Free Conscience," reprint, Syracuse Law Review, Fall 1953, also typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Poetry and Tradition," Sewanee Review, Oct 1940 (Box 15)
    - "The Poetry of A.E. Housman" (Box 15)
    - "Politics and Mr. Crosskey's Constitution I," reprint, Syracuse Law Review, Spring 1955, also draft A, original typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Politics and Mr. Crosskey's Constitution II," reprint, Syracuse Law Review, Fall 1955, also draft A, original typescript rev.; draft B, typescript copy (Box 15)
    - "Problems in Democratic Citizenship, with Michael O. Sawyer, reprint from Journal of Higher Education, Feb 1952 (Box 15)
    - "Some Poems of Louis MacNeice," Sewanee Review, Winter 1943 (Box 15)
    - "Success for a Lame Duck", 1968; draft A, typescript rev,; draft B, repro. (Box 15)
    - "Teaching the Documents of American Democracy," Social Education, May 1948 (Box 16)
    - "Thoughts on the Present State of Liberalism in America", draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript revised; draft C, typescript (Box 16)
    - "Toward an American Tradition; Paul Elmer More as Critic" (Box 16)
    - "Two American Platonists: Santayana and P.E. More", typescript (Box 16)
  - Book reviews
    - American Constitutional Custom: A Forgotten Factor in the Founding, by Burleigh Cushing Rodick, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - Americans and Chinese: Two Ways of Life, by Francis L. K. Hay, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - Democratic Foundations: Classic or Pragmatic, re: The Moral Foundation of Democracy, by John H. Hallowell and Civil Liberties and the Vinson Court, by C. Herman Pritchell, typescript copy (Box 16)
    - Essay in Politics, by Scott Buchanan and The Conservative Mind: From Burke to Santayana, by Russell Kirk, typescript copy rev. (Box 16)
    - Freedom Limited: An Essay on Democracy by Marten Ten Hoor; The Individual and the New World, by John M. Anderson and The Liberal Tradition in America, by Louis Hartz, typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Genius of American Politics, by Daniel Boorstin, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Heir Apparent: Robert Kennedy and the Struggle for Power, by William V. Shannon, typescript rev. (Box 16)
    - The Papers of James Madison, Vol. III, ed. by W.T. Hutchinson and William M.E. Rachal, typescript copy (Box 16)
      See also Correspondence: The Historical Society of Pennsylvania.
    - The Papers of James Madison, Vol. IV, ed. by W.T. Hutchinson and William M.E. Rachal, typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Papers of James Madison, Vol V, ed. by W.T. Hutchinson and William M.E. Rachal, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Politics of Honor: A Biography of Adlai E. Stevenson, by Kenneth Davis and Adlai Stevenson: A Study in Values, by Herbert J. Muller, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Radical Papers, ed. by Irving Howe, repro. from Ethics, vol. 77, also typescript rev. (Box 16)
    - Roger Williams: His Contribution to the American Tradition, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - Seedtime of the Republic: The Origin of the American Tradition of Political Liberty, by Clinton Rossiter, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Spirit of 'Seventy-Six, ed. by Henry Steele Commager and Richard B. Morris, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The Uncommon Defense and Congress, 1945-1963, by Edward Kolodziej, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 16)
    - The United States and Canada, by Gerald M. Craig, repro. from Annals, vol. 378, also typescript rev. (Box 16)
  - Books
    - Alexander Hamilton
      - Draft A, typescript copy rev. (Box 16)
      - Draft B, typescript rev. (Box 16)
    - Aspects of American Democracy and Culture, with Ralph Henry Gabriel and Alpheus Thomas Mason (Box 16)
    - The Bonnie Prince, Chapters I-VI, VIII, typescript rev. (Box 17)
    - Conscience in Politics
      - Research material
        - Eisenhower Administration, 1956 (Box 17)
        - Eleanor Roosevelt letters, 1948-1956; typescript reproduction (Box 17)
        - Foreign policy, 1956; includes notes on Brown conversation with Morris Bernstein (Box 17)
        - Formosa, 1958; includes typescript copy and typescript reproduction of. A.E. Stevenson speeches (Box 17)
        - McCarthyism, includes typescript of Stevenson press conferences, typescript repro, of Stevenson's 1952-1953 speeches (Box 17)
        - Middle East - Suez (Box 17)
        - A.E. Stevenson, articles by, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
        - 1956 Stevenson primary campaign, includes typescript copy transcript of speech and interview (Stevenson) (Box 17)
        - Stevenson for president, 1960?, 1958-1960 (Box 17)
        - Stevenson for President Committee, 1956 (Box 17)
        - Stevenson speeches
          - Speeches New York Times, 1952-1958 (Box 17)
          - Speeches, 1957-1959; typescript copy; typescript reproduction (Box 18)
          - Speeches, Sep 1960; typescript reproduction (Box 18)
          - Speeches, Oct-Dec 1960; typescript reproduction (Box 18)
        - Chapter VII, 1958; includes typescript reproduction of radio symposium with A.E. Stevenson and typescript reproduction of Stevenson speeches (Box 18)
        - Chapter VIII, 1959; includes typescript reproduction, Stevenson speech (Box 18)
        - Chapter IX, 1960; includes typescript reproduction, Stevenson speeches, correspondence (Box 18)
      - Draft A, 1961; typescript reproduction with penciled holograph annotations by Adlai E. Stevenson; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Draft B, typescript copy (Box 19)
      - Draft C, typescript rev.; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Afterword, typescript rev. (Box 19)
    - The Frame of Government, with H. Bragdon and S. McCutcheon, preface, holograph and typescript (Box 19)
    - Internationalism and Democracy, ed. by S.G. Brown
      - Typescript copy, incomplete, 1949 (Box 19)
      - Bills and receipts, 1950-1951 (Box 19)
      - Book reviews, 1950 (Box 19)
    - James Monroe, proposal only, typescript copy (Box 19)
    - Jefferson
      - Draft A, typescript rev. (Box 19)
      - Draft B, typescript copy rev. (Box 19)
    - John Jay Chapman and Other Essays on Individualism in America
      - Draft A, typescript and typescript copy (Box 20)
      - Draft B, typescript rev. (Box 20)
      - Draft C, typescript copy (Box 20)
    - The Limits of Democratic Compromise
      - Draft A, typescript rev. (Box 20)
      - Draft B, typescript copy (Box 20)
    - Major American Philosophies, ed. by S.G. Brown, incomplete, typescript and typescript copy (Box 20)
    - Masters of American Literature, prospectus only, typescript copy (Box 20)
    - On Being Civilized, 1946; draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 20)
    - One Mind's Life: Recollections and Reminiscences [autobiography], undated; typescript (Box 26)
      Gift of Robert J. Wilson, 2020.
    - re: Precinct workers, outline only, 1952; typescript copy (Box 20)
    - The Religious Philosophy of Josiah Royce, ed. By S.G. Brown, 1953; introduction, draft A, holo; draft B, typescript rev.; draft C, typescript copy; book reviews (Box 20)
    - The Social Philosophy of Josiah Royce, ed. By S.G. Brown, preface and chapter only, draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript copy; book review (Box 20)
    - We Hold These Truths, table of contents only, Jan 1949; typescript copy; also book reviews (Box 20)
  - Citation "William Averell Harriman" (Box 20)
  - Course Materials
    - Civics for Americans (Box 20)
    - Compromise of 1850 (Box 20)
    - Political Science Outlines (Box 21)
  - Course description, Social Science 300, typescript copy (Box 21)
  - Essays
    - Lucretius and Modern Materialism, typescript copy (Box 21)
    - A New Era for Publius: T.V. Smith and the Art of Politics, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B typescript copy (Box 21)
    - On Being Free, draft A, typescript revs; draft B typescript copy (Box 21)
  - Lectures
    - Communism, Democracy and Education, draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript rev.; draft C typescript copy (Box 21)
    - Democratic Manifesto I, typescript (Box 21)
    - Democratic Manifesto II, draft A, holo.; draft B, typescript copy; draft C, typescript rev.; draft D typescript copy (Box 21)
    - Memo to Americans, lectures given at University of Hawaii
      - Memo for Americans No. 9, circa 1962; brown_sg_001; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
      - Memo for Americans No. 10, circa 1962; brown_sg_002; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
      - Memo for Americans No. 11, circa 1962; brown_sg_003; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
      - Memo for Americans No. 12, circa 1962; brown_sg_004; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
      - Memo for Americans No. 13, circa 1962; brown_sg_005; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
      - Memo for Americans No. 14, circa 1962; brown_sg_006; envelope says "First Term Lecture Series (University of Hawaii)"; Flexi Disc (Box 21)
    - Lectures for Citizenship IA, 1947-1948; typescript (Box 21)
    - The Role of Communication in Citizenship, Oct 5 1948; typescript (Box 21)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1952-1958; holograph, typescript and typescript copy rev. (Box 21)
  - Notes, 1947-1963; holograph, typescript (Box 21)
  - Radio discussion
    - Who Are Today's Conservatives?, University of Chicago Round Table, Feb 27, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Radio speeches for Adlai E. Stevenson
    - Station WAGE, Nov 1952, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript (Box 21)
    - Station WOLF, Nov 1952, draft A, typescript rev.; draft B, typescript (Box 21)
  - Reports
    - Conference on Constitutional Rights and Liberties, Oct 11-12, 1960; typescript reproduction (Box 21)
    - The Kennedy Campaign's Final Week: The Need For Fresh Emphasis, typescript reproduction (Box 21)
    - of Committee on Research - The Political Career of James Monroe, Year Book of the American Philosophical Society, 1959 (Box 21)